[whimpering]
♪
- Oh, Kazuma!
- I'm Kazuma!
Death's icy grip
should not have taken thee!
You're enjoying this, huh?
I've always wanted to say that.
- [AQUA] Kazuma!
- I'm Kazuma!
[AQUA]
I'm done reviving your body,
so you think you could
hurry it up a little?
Darkness is really stinky
and depressed for some reason!
Now, stop wasting time
and let's go!
You need to get moving!
Come on!
[both chuckle]
- [gasps]
- [chuckles]
That's better.
Welcome home, Kazuma.
What is that nasty smell?
And how did I end up naked?
All your clothes were digested.
Your sword with the weird name
is the only thing
that's left here.
Hang on.
There is nothing "weird"
about the name
of that blade and, no,
I'm not just saying that
'cause I came up with it!
♪
Hey, Darkness.
Eris mentioned something.
Did you really
let the Hydra swallow
you up to rescue me?
Hmm.
Doesn't sound like you at all.
♪
Well, let's head home
and hit the bath!
- Y' know, Kazuma.
- [KAZUMA] Hmm?
Asking her to do that
while you aren't
wearing any clothes
isn't the best look.
- [MEGUMIN] Are you a pervert?
- [gasps]
Are you a pervert?
All right,
it's time for you two
to get in the bath fast
especially since Kazuma's gonna
get reported, at this rate.
Shut up!
Is the Hydra
still gonna be a problem?
Well, not for a while, anyway.
It'll probably be tied up
re-fouling the lake.
All thanks to me,
the Goddess who purified it!
[MEGUMIN] Whenever you seem
sure of something,
it feels like there's a pitfall
that's lying in wait.
[scoffs]
Oh, really? Unbelievable!
Keep on talking like that
and I'm gonna have Kazuma
or Darkness carry you instead!
[whimpering]
Uh, no! I apologize, okay?
Please! Anything but that!
[AQUA]
We need to get going, then.
We've gotta try and talk up
what we did out there
as best as we can!
That way, even if we
don't get the full reward
for taking that monster down,
we could still get our grubby
little hands on some gold!
[MEGUMIN]
Leave everything to me!
The glorious wonders
of my explosion magic
are something I can go into
great detail about!
[sighs]
[KAZUMA] According
to Aqua being digested
by the Hydra turned me into
more of a "Kazuma-chan."
Uh.
Oh, man, this is the same size
it was before, right?
- [DARKNESS] Kazuma.
- Yeah? I'm Kazuma-chan?"
[DARKNESS]
You seem to be taking a while.
- Are you hurt anywhere?
- No, no, I'm okay!
[KAZUMA]
You remember how bad we stunk!
Just wanted to scrub
every itch.
[water splashing]
Just so you know, I, I regret
forcing the issue this time.
Yeah, well,
what's done is done!
Aqua and Megumin
are probably chowing down
at the guild now,
so we ought to hurry on
over there.
Indeed, we should get going.
Huh?
[DARKNESS] I will leave your
change of clothes here for you.
[KAZUMA]
Hey, uh, is there some reason
you needed to take
that Hydra down?
[gasps]
No, no, not at all!
- I mean, how could there be?
- [KAZUMA] So, there is.
- That's so weird to ask.
- [KAZUMA] I know it didn't
exactly work out today,
but the next time
we go after that thing,
we'll come up
with a legit plan first.
- Okay?
- [Darkness gasps]
What's the matter with you?
After all that hot air
you kept on blowing
about protecting the town
you aren't giving up already, right?
Never! It seems
you have forgotten who I am!
As per my Dustiness bloodline
it is my sworn duty
to defend others.
So, the next chance we get,
that Hydra is dead meat!
- [DARKNESS] Hmm?
- Hmm.
[MORGAN]
I can't believe this!
How do you people always manage
to make things worse?
You guys just had to piss off
something as nasty as a Hydra!
[YUNYUN]
Oh, my goodness, Megumin!
This sounds awful!
- What did you do this time?
- Hmm?
- [tavern patrons complaining]
- [whimpering]
[gasps]
Kazuma!
What's got 'em all so riled up?
Since a squadron of knights
was being deployed
I thought the quest was posted
as a stopgap measure.
[chuckles]
About that.
Seems there's been
a bit of an incident
in the Royal Capital.
The Capital?
[IRIS]
Big Brother!
Now tell me!
Is the Capital in trouble?
Is my cute little sister
in some kinda danger right now?
Well, apparently some group
calling themselves
the Silver-Haired Thief Brigade
managed to sneak
into the Royal Castle.
[LUNA] And the knights
all have their hands full
trying to recover the treasures
that were stolen.
♪
[KAZUMA]
Holy crap.
I've got a bounty on my head
like a Devil King general.
Wait a minute,
if some capital city crooks
have their bounties posted
in our town then...
Okay,
you didn't hear this from me
but the authorities consulted
a Crimson Demon fortune teller
about their true identities.
[LUNA]
And that 200 million bounty
is hiding right under our noses
here in Axel!
- [both gasp]
- [ALL] 200 mill?
Hey, are you serious?
'Cause that's a lot juicier
than taking down some monsters!
So, the Silver-Haired
Thief Brigade
is actually here in this town,
as we speak?
- [whimpering]
- Interesting.
200 million, huh?
[both whimpering]
Huh! Hey, come on!
What're you looking at me for?
[LUNA] Everyone!
If we're able to capture
the Silver-Haired
Thief Brigade,
then the knights will come to
Axel and deal with the Hydra!
So, with that being the case
we'll be expecting you to help,
as well, Kazuma!
Sure! Of course! No problem!
I'd love to help out!
[ALL]
Konosuba!
[AQUA] ♪ Little dragon
calm and serene ♪
[KAZUMA]
And, of course, I decided
- to stay locked indoors.
- ♪ Go to sleep ♪
♪ and have a sweet dream ♪
♪ When you're born ♪
♪ My wish will come true ♪
♪ I'll take care of you ♪
[KAZUMA]
What's with the lullaby?
Prenatal bonding!
Right!
You don't have to lie beside
the egg like that, ya know.
Leaving it there by
the fireplace should be fine.
And if it ends up cooked,
we can always eat it.
[grunts]
You seem kinda hungry!
So why don't you try
a holy knuckle sandwich?
I'm channeling my powers
into the egg!
And that way, I can make sure
he'll reign over
all the other dragons!
As his mom I'll do
whatever I can to help him!
Then again,
you already know that,
now don't you my Emperor Zel?
[KAZUMA] That has gotta be
the stupidest name.
Kazuma! It's go time!
If the Hydra won't fall
from a single blow,
then we'll continue
to strike away until it does!
Huh?
[MEGUMIN] As with
the Mobile Fortress Destroyer,
Aqua's magic power
and your drain touch
are what we need
to take it down for good!
- Yeah, no.
- [gasps]
Why should I head out there
and fight this thing
by submitting to some
disgusting Lich skill?
My holy magic power
isn't meant to be
shared with everyone
at the drop of a hat, ya know!
I don't care
if Kazuma threatens me,
if Darkness
tries buttering me up,
or if you go totally crazy,
Megumin,
'cause I'm not gonna do it!
[gasps]
[KAZUMA]
What is up with you?
Why are you so fired up
for revenge, anyway?
Uh. It's simple.
This is the same monster
that took your life.
So, why wouldn't I want to try
and avenge that?
I...I see.
[MEGUMIN] Up to this point,
we've been using
Darkness' Decoy skill
every day,
and then
we always follow that up
with a blast of Explosion Magic
to harass it.
But, I'm still wondering
if there isn't
a more effective strategy.
What the hell, Darkness?
You didn't say anything?
It's your job to stop her
when she gets like this!
W-Well, sometimes...
but it is quite important
that The Hydra is dealt with.
And, besides this should be
fairly effective
at whittling down
its magical power.
[KAZUMA]
These two.
We're outta luck
as long as it keeps raining.
That just gives the thing
an advantage.
The fortune tellers say
this rain isn't going to be
letting up any time soon.
I'll get serious
when the sun comes out.
[both gasp]
- [cat meowing]
- [gasps]
So, you weren't going to do
anything about this
in the foreseeable future?
[KAZUMA] What the hell?
Give her back to me!
I need my Chomusuke!
Put her down!
You got that? Gimme the cat
or face the consequences!
♪
[explosion]
[Megumin fainting]
[KAZUMA]
In the days that followed,
the rain still didn't let up.
But, that didn't stop
Darkness and Megumin.
They just kept on paying visits
to the Hydra.
[MEGUMIN]
Hey, we're home!
Darkness is a bit of a mess,
so could you get
the bath ready for her?
[Darkness panting]
[KAZUMA] Seriously,
you've gotta stop this.
It's dangerous.
That monster.
It must be bothered
by all the Explosion magic
because it ambushed us.
[DARKNESS]
Megumin landed her spell,
which gave us
the chance to flee
while it was regenerating.
This is proving to be
much harder than I thought.
Thanks so much, Aqua.
- [AQUA] Mm-hmm.
- Uh!
♪
[growling]
[sighs]
♪ My sweet dragon
so safe and warm ♪
♪ I can't wait
until you are born ♪
♪ Mother's here
for all that you do ♪
[DARKNESS]
Kazuma. What are you doing?
Got pretty bored,
so I'm fixing your armor.
There's really nothing' else
to do here,
with all this rain.
You better not run out there
when I'm done, either.
Hmm.
This reminds me.
You repaired my armor
once before
back when we were on our way
to the hot springs.
You know we should all
go there again, sometime.
There's no way in hell.
I can't stand that place.
It feels like a whole town
full of Megumins.
[MEGUMIN]
Hey, and what exactly
is that supposed to mean, anyway?
Excuse me? Come on!
How could you be so cruel
to my adoring faithful?
You, too, Aqua?
Guess I'm confused, so maybe
you can explain this!
I just mean that my faithful
are really sweet
and earnest types!
Even so going would be nice.
[birds chirping]
Kazuma!
Darkness has gone missing!
And her equipment isn't here,
either!
[KAZUMA] Dammit! I kept on
tellin' her not to go!
It's too dangerous to do alone!
Unbelievable!
That girl is so unbelievable!
First, I'm gonna drop off
the egg with Wiz,
then I'll give Darkness
a piece of my mind!
[sighs]
All right!
The two of you
need to go on ahead
- and try to slow her down!
- You're leaving?
I've gotta head out
and make a few stops!
No matter what, do not
let her fight by herself!
Damn it, Darkness!
I guess we're doin' this!
[roughneck sighs]
I don't like the look
of that sky.
It's making
all my old scars ache.
[DARKNESS]
Let go of me!
Unbelievable!
You're being so unbelievable!
It's too dangerous to do alone!
Wait, is the reason
you aren't giving up
'cause you think
we're gonna yell at you?
We won't get mad!
Just come back home! Please!
What in the world's gotten
into you?
Tell us what's going on,
Darkness!
I thought we were friends!
[DARKNESS] That may be true
but, even so, I...
Uh.
- [CROWD] Darkness!
- [gasps]
[crowd chanting Darkness!]
[MAN 01]
Trying to get away, huh?
What the...
[ALL]
Lalatina!
Hey, do not call me that!
[DARKNESS]
What is going on here?
If this is some new type
of harassment,
I will not put up with it!
No, no, you don't understand!
It's nothing like that!
I swear!
I was just telling everybody
how you kept fighting
the Hydra,
and asked 'em if they wanted
to try and help out!
Kazuma has really been keeping
the booze flowing for us, lately.
So, we figured we oughta
return the favor
and pay the lad back a little.
And, we can help take care
of your issue
while we're at it, Lalatina.
[sighs]
See there? Check it out.
[KAZUMA] All of these
hardcore adventurers
have gathered together out
here for you.
And, I know you've got
muscles for brains
but try your best not to
make 'em worry, all right?
Everyone...
Hey, get a load of that!
Lalatina's embarrassed!
Ha-ha!
[AQUA]
Blessing!
And even more Blessings!
If you're in the thief class,
then get ready with Bind!
Archers, set up your roped
arrows and standby!
We're taking on a Hydra!
So, stay focused
[ADVENTURERS]
Right!
Wizards, no need to worry
about a second shot!
Just give us
all your magic power
and be prepared for a big one!
Leave it to me!
My Explosion magic
is about to turn that Hydra
into a big pile
of burning cinders!
Now listen, Darkness!
Your Decoy skill is the key
to this entire plan!
So don't go down too fast!
Right!
Okay.
Let's go!
♪
[AQUA]
Blessing! Blessing! Blessing!
Now, Darkness!
Consider it good as done!
Decoy!
You're dead meat!
[howling]
Aah!
[panting]
[KAZUMA]
Good! Thief skill squad!
[THIEVES]
And Bind!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
[panting]
[ARCHER 08-A]
Wind speed's good.
So's the line of sight.
All right,
just a little higher!
Good, good, good,
good, good, good.
Okay, right there! Stop!
Fire!
[gasps]
[SAKAMAKI]
We got 'em!
- Hurry! Grab on!
- Pull! Pull!
Pull that thing!
Give it all that you've got!
[ADVENTURERS]
Heave Ho!
[Hydra growling]
Are you sure about this,
Kazuma?
Yeah, send me
right at that thing!
Ah! Aah!
[grunts]
If this monster won't go down
till its power's gone,
then I'll take it all!
[KAZUMA]
Drain Touch!
♪
[roaring]
We can't lose!
It's working, you guys!
Aah!
[thuds]
[screaming] Good job!
We've got him now!
[DARKNESS]
Kazuma!
[Kazuma whimpering]
Everyone!
[growling]
[Kazuma whimpering]
[KAZUMA]
I'm impressed, Dustiness.
Look at all that strength
and endurance you've got.
Now would not be the time!
[DARKNESS] [groaning] I cannot
hold out for much longer.
[KAZUMA] Hang in there,
dumbass! You have to!
Drain Touch! Drain Touch!
Darkness has really
taken a beating
to chip away
at this thing's magic power.
And, I won't
let it go to waste!
Don't give up, Darkness,
we need you to keep going.
This is too much.
Damn it, you're finally being
useful for once
and you're giving up already?
I thought you were a hell
of a lot stronger than that!
- [gasps]
- Gimme a break!
No way you'll win
an endurance contest
like this being so soft!
Ya gutless wimp!
Being pulverized by a Hydra
while taking
a creep's verbal abuse.
This is absolutely
exhilarating!
- Heave Ho! Heave Ho!
- Pull harder!
She can't take much more!
Don't screw with Axel's
adventurers, scale face!
[grunts]
The others.
Kazuma go not worry.
We will die together.
I am very worried!
Stop giving up!
You'd never die
from having a Hydra
flopping on top of you!
[KAZUMA] I'm the only one
who's gonna get
smooshed to death here!
[gasps]
[DARKNESS]
If I give up right now,
then Kazuma will die?
[DARKNESS] [whimpering]
What is this?
[whimpering]
I have never felt
this way before.
You are ordering me around
as if you were my master.
Yet, your very life
is in my hands!
What a paradox.
That is such
a bold contradiction!
[whimpering]
So, in this situation,
which one of us
is truly the master?
Kazuma what novel stimulation!
[screaming]
[Hydra groaning]
It looks like the hydra's
getting weaker!
- [laughs]
- [gasps]
I'm gonna collect that big-time
bounty, you guys!
The reward goes
to whoever lands
the finishing blow, remember?
What the hell are you saying
at a time like this?
Nobody's getting
a cut of my loo--
[RIN]
No! Dust!
[Kazuma groaning]
Light of Saber!
Look do you see that?
Its head isn't growing back!
All right, wizards!
Time to do your thing!
[MEGUMIN]
A looming tide of sorrows.
An overflowing swell of screams
coiling into one another
forming the howling vortex
that marks our victory!
Let the signal of Oblivion
now descend upon you!
This is my offering
to the deceased.
May he rest in eternal peace.
Vengeance for Kazuma!
[KAZUMA]
Hey, I'm still alive!
[MEGUMIN]
Explosion!
[explosion]
[tavern patrons cheering]
[indistinct chatter]
It's pretty crazy
what you can pull off
when you get desperate,
isn't it?
Hey, Kazuma, you guys
can take a bigger cut!
For trying to cheat everyone
take this jerk's
cut of the reward too.
- Huh?
- [laughs]
How does it feel
to have finally
taken down that Hydra?
Think you'll be able
to sleep better?
Yes, and I have
a whole new perspective, now.
So many things
that used to trouble me
seem so foolish, in hindsight.
[DARKNESS]
But, it has nothing
to do with the Hydra
being destroyed.
Actually, I was just reminded
of how special the people
in this town are to me
and how much I truly love them.
I have no more doubts
about that.
[KAZUMA] You say some really
embarrassing stuff sometimes.
I guess I do.
I just feel blessed.
Uh-uh?
[AQUA] You need to show me
a little more respect!
Or, did you already forget
that I resurrected you?
Where is the appreciation
I so rightfully deserve?
[DUST]
Damn it, Kazuma!
That priest of yours is being
a huge pain in the ass!
- [MEGUMIN, AQUA] We're home!
- [KAZUMA] Welcome back!
Yo, Darkness! You came
back here pretty early, huh?
[MEGUMIN]
Hey, I don't see her anywhere.
[KAZUMA]
Is she in her room?
Well, it's time for a few more
drinky drinks!
Bring Darkness out here
'cause the three of us
are gonna empty this bottle!
- [MEGUMIN] Kazuma.
- [BOTH] Huh?
[KAZUMA]
What's this?
[AQUA]
Whatcha got there?
"Please forgive me for suddenly
springing this on you."
- Whoa, what the...
- [both gasp]
[DARKNESS]
Please forgive me for suddenly
springing this on you.
I am sorry.
But, things have become
rather complex
I realize this is selfish
but I am afraid
I have to leave.
To that end,
I ask that you find
a new frontline fighter
for the group.
I am very grateful
to the three of you.
So much so that I could never
fully express my feelings.
Aqua, Megumin, Kazuma.
I wanted you to know
our adventures have been
the most wonderful moments
of my entire life,
and I treasure them.
There is no doubt in my mind
that the days
we all spent together
will be forever etched
in my memory.
Thank you for everything
from Lalatina Dustiness Ford
to my beloved companions
with deep gratitude.
Meow.
[HANS] The end of the line
starts right here!
[laughs] You're gonna like
what we've got!
Guess it doesn't make sense
to open this kinda letter.
It's actually
my business's sloga--